What keeps you motivated to keep going and
keep kind of getting after it, pursuing tech,
creating more companies?
What is it that keeps you motivated?
Well, I did that for a while.
I burnt out.
I had worked so hard at so young that
when I immediately sold my company, I thought that's
all I want to do.
I want to travel.
And I bought a large yacht and traveled
the world for many years and thought that's what
I would do for the rest of my life until
all of a sudden, I think if you're an entrepreneur,
you just can't sit still and the boredom sets in.
And you have to be careful with boredom because
in that situation, I used to say the happy
hour can get earlier and earlier every day.
You find yourself going, what am I
going to do to cure this boredom?
And if you're in a creative person,
you're an entrepreneur, you're always going to create
and just acknowledge that and
find something you enjoy doing.
That's why I've had kind of these different
kind of businesses and sub careers just because
I pick things that I
find interesting and want to do.